export const Comics = [
  {
    no: 1,
    question: "Who is the alter ego of Batman?",
    A: "Bruce Banner",
    B: "Peter Parker",
    C: "Clark Kent",
    D: "Bruce Wayne",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    no: 2,
    question: "Which superhero is known as the Man of Steel?",
    A: "Spider-Man",
    B: "Iron Man",
    C: "Superman",
    D: "Captain America",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    no: 3,
    question: "What is the real name of Spider-Man?",
    A: "Tony Stark",
    B: "Steve Rogers",
    C: "Peter Parker",
    D: "Matt Murdock",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    no: 4,
    question: "Which superhero wields the Mjolnir hammer?",
    A: "Thor",
    B: "Hulk",
    C: "Black Widow",
    D: "Wolverine",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    no: 5,
    question: "Who is the arch-nemesis of the Flash?",
    A: "Lex Luthor",
    B: "Green Goblin",
    C: "Joker",
    D: "Reverse-Flash",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    no: 6,
    question: "Which superhero is also known as Diana Prince?",
    A: "Storm",
    B: "Wonder Woman",
    C: "Black Canary",
    D: "Rogue",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    no: 7,
    question: "What radioactive arachnid bite granted Peter Parker his powers?",

    A: "A radioactive scorpion",
    B: "A radioactive mosquito",
    C: "A radioactive spider",
    D: "A radioactive ant",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    no: 8,
    question: "Who is the founder of the X-Men?",

    A: "Magneto",
    B: "Cyclops",
    C: "Professor X",
    D: "Wolverine",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    no: 9,
    question: "Which superhero is known for his adamantium skeleton?",

    A: "Deadpool",
    B: "Iron Fist",
    C: "Hawkeye",
    D: "Wolverine",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    no: 10,
    question: "Who is the butler of Bruce Wayne?",

    A: "Alfred Pennyworth",
    B: "James Gordon",
    C: "Harvey Dent",
    D: "Lucius Fox",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    no: 11,
    question: "Which superhero is known for his vibranium shield?",

    A: "Black Panther",
    B: "Iron Man",
    C: "Captain America",
    D: "Hulk",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    no: 12,
    question: "What is the alter ego of the Green Lantern?",

    A: "Hal Jordan",
    B: "Barry Allen",
    C: "Oliver Queen",
    D: "Arthur Curry",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    no: 13,
    question:
      "Which superhero is known for his telepathic and telekinetic abilities?",

    A: "Nightcrawler",
    B: "Beast",
    C: "Iceman",
    D: "Jean Grey",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    no: 14,
    question: "Who is the love interest of Mary Jane Watson in Spider-Man?",

    A: "Harry Osborn",
    B: "Eddie Brock",
    C: "Gwen Stacy",
    D: "Peter Parker",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    no: 15,
    question: "Which superhero is a founding member of the Fantastic Four?",

    A: "Silver Surfer",
    B: "Black Widow",
    C: "Invisible Woman",
    D: "Scarlet Witch",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    no: 16,
    question: "Who is the vigilante alter ego of Oliver Queen?",

    A: "Hawkeye",
    B: "Green Arrow",
    C: "Deadshot",
    D: "Black Canary",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    no: 17,
    question: "Which villain is known as the 'Merc with a Mouth'?",

    A: "Joker",
    B: "Penguin",
    C: "Two-Face",
    D: "Deadpool",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    no: 18,
    question: "Who is the telepathic leader of the New Mutants?",

    A: "Colossus",
    B: "Wolfsbane",
    C: "Psylocke",
    D: "Cable",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    no: 19,
    question: "What is the real name of the Hulk?",

    A: "Bruce Wayne",
    B: "Tony Stark",
    C: "Bruce Banner",
    D: "Clark Kent",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    no: 20,
    question: "Which superhero has retractable adamantium claws?",

    A: "Black Panther",
    B: "Iron Fist",
    C: "Hawkeye",
    D: "Wolverine",
    answer: "D",
  },
];
